nairapark.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - NairaPark

The website www.nairapark.com shall henceforth be called "Nairapark.com". By accessing or using Nairapark.com, you agree to have read and understood the Privacy Policy as stipulated below: 

If you decide to use any of our services, you may be requested to provide information about yourself. You are not obliged to provide any information although if you do not, certain services may not be made available to you. If you do provide any personal information, you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information which is not misleading in any way. If you decide to change any of your personal information such as your e-mail address, you may wish to inform us. Simply send an e-mail to admin@nairapark.com so as to make necessary amendment. 

By accessing Nairapark.com, you consent to the use of your information as set out in this policy even though changes are made to this privacy policy continuously. Your continuous use of Nairapark.com or our services therefore signifies that you agree to such changes. 

We use certain information supplied to communicate with you. We may also use these information for statistics and other information relating to your use of our site and our services for the purpose of monitoring our website usage in order to help us develop the website and improve generally on our services. Subsequently, we may also share some information you provided with third parties for the purpose of giving you special offers we might not be able to give you but we shall not be held responsible for their operations, including, but not limited to, their information practices. 

Occasionally, we may wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you but if you would rather not want to receive such information, kindly send an e-mail to admin@nairapark.com describing your resentment. 

We collect visitors' contact information. This information is used to send orders and information about our company to our visitors. We also use this information to get in touch with their experience on our site and show them contents according to their preference. 

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. nairapark.com respect Google Adsense Privacy Policy as contained in <https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms> Please note that Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on nairapark.com. Google's use of cookies enable it to serve ads to users based on their visit to nairapark.com and other sites on the Internet. You can learn more about how google handle privacy issues or may opt out of the use of the cookie by visiting the Google ad content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>, <http://www.google.com/intl/en/contact/> or <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. 

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site and these ads may contain cookies. Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website. In order to have full access to Nairapark.com, you are required to enable JavaScript and cookies in your browser. 

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access Nairapark.com. Please notify us if any part of this policy is not clear to you or if you have any suggestion that could help us improve our policy or site at large. You may wish to correct or request a copy of your information that is with us at any time. Remember to send further enquiries to info@nairapark.com
